phonebooks.com 2019-02-01

# PhoneBooks.com Privacy Policy

| 

## Lookup SOMEONE  
  
---|---  
  
## **Privacy Policy**

At PhoneBooks.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. We do not currently sell information to third parties nor do we have plans to do so. At your request we will remove your personal information from this site ([click here](https://www.phonebooks.com/contact.html) for instructions on how to do this).

**NOTE: WE DO NOT SHARE ANY INFORMATION WITH TELEMARKETERS.** Telemarketing to cell phones is **illegal** and strictly enforced by the FTC ([more information here](http://www.ftc.gov/opa/2005/04/dnc.shtm)). This service is offered to benefit users and help people find someone they are looking for.

The following is information on what types of personal information we may receive and collect when you use and visit PhoneBooks.com, and how we safeguard your information. 

Log Files  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on PhoneBooks.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
